{
    "subject": "resource/Orson_Welles",
    "predicate": "property/parents",
    "object": "Richard Hodgdon Head Welles",
    "human_readable": "The parents of Orson Welles are Richard Hodgdon Head Welles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9034491181373596,
            "question": "Who are the parents of Orson Welles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7675095796585083,
            "question": "Was Richard Hodgdon Head Welles a famous actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7617517709732056,
            "question": "What is the name of Orson Welles' mother?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7058767676353455,
            "question": "What is the name of Orson Welles' father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6299328804016113,
            "question": "Did Orson Welles have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.590912401676178,
            "question": "How did the names of Orson Welles' parents influence his upbringing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5857976675033569,
            "question": "Did Orson Welles' parents have any influence on his career choices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4817412197589874,
            "question": "Was Orson Welles known for any specific acting style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4006182849407196,
            "question": "What is Orson Welles best remembered for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28503161668777466,
            "question": "What are some famous works directed by Orson Welles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The parents of Orson Welles are Richard Hodgdon Head Welles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5425_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Orson Welles best remembered for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5425_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Orson Welles known for any specific acting style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5425_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Orson Welles' parents have any influence on his career choices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5425_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5425_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that the parents of Orson Welles are  \"Beatrice (n\u00e9e Ives) and Richard Hodgdon Head Welles\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents confirm that Orson Welles' father was indeed named Richard Head Welles (also referred to as Richard Hodgdon Head Welles in some documents)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the family lineage of Orson Welles, including his father's name as Richard Head Welles. Therefore, the statement that the parents of Orson Welles include Richard Hodgdon Head Welles is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It contradicts information provided about Orson Welles' parents being Richard Hodgdon Head Welles and Beatrice (Ives) Welles.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}